https://mcm.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
The Minnesota Children’s Museum is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust. Accordingly, we maintain the following privacy policy to protect personal information provided by you.
Personal Information that Minnesota Children’s Museum May Collect Online
Minnesota Children’s Museum collects the following types of personal information: names, postal and email addresses, phone and facsimile numbers, billing information, and complaint information.
Minnesota Children’s Museum does not knowingly collect or maintain any personal information from children under the age of 13.
How Minnesota Children’s Museum May Use Personal Information Collected Online
Unless you consent otherwise, Minnesota Children’s Museum will use your personal information only for the purpose for which it was submitted, such as to replying to inquiries, handling your complaints, and processing billing and business requests related to program participation. At any time you may add or remove your name from our mailing list by contacting us or by calling 651-225-6000.
How Your Information May Be Shared
From time to time, Minnesota Children’s Museum will trade email lists with other like-minded organizations. You may opt out of the list trades at anytime by contacting us or call 651-225-6000.
Help Us Keep Your Personal Information Accurate
If your personal information changes or you would like to review the personal information we may have on file, please email us with the new information or your review request contacting us.
Problems
If you have a complaint about Minnesota Children’s Museum’s compliance with this privacy policy, you may contact us by contacting us or calling 651-225-6000.
Photography Permission Policy
Periodically, the Minnesota Children’s Museum takes photographs and video of Museum visitors and activities for use in promotional and editorial material. With admission into the Museum, you give permission to the Museum for the recording of photographs and/or video of yourself and your dependents. You grant the Museum all rights to use these still or moving images for educational, promotional, advertising, and other purposes which advance the overall mission of the Museum, “to spark children’s learning through play.” All rights to the photographs and video belong to the Museum. Please notify the Box Office if you do not consent to this policy.
Minnesota Children’s Museum 10 West Seventh Street St. Paul, MN 55102 651-225-6000 Fax: 651-225-6006 Contact Us | Privacy Policy
Give a Membership Accessibility
News Blog Contact Info Media Resources
AboutAnnual ReportLeadership & BoardEmployment
Museum Professionals
Traveling Exhibit Rentals
Explore Our Research
Support the museum with a reoccuring donation!
Support the museum with a recurring donation!
$ Donation Amount:
$1.00$5.00$10.00$20.00$25.00Custom Amount
Make this donation every dayweekmonthquarteryear
Select Payment Method
PayPal
Personal Info
First Name									*
Last Name
Email Address									*
Make this an anonymous donation.
Billing Details
Country									*
United StatesCanadaUnited KingdomAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarrussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongo, Democratic People's RepublicCongo, Republic ofCook IslandsCosta RicaCote d'IvoireCroatia/HrvatskaCubaCyprus IslandCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEquatorial GuineaEl SalvadorEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGreeceGhanaGibraltarGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHoly See (City Vatican State)HondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyan Arab JamahiriyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldova, Republic ofMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoriesPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn IslandPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunion IslandRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovak RepublicSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth GeorgiaSouth KoreaSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsEswatiniSwedenSwitzerlandSyrian Arab RepublicTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaTogoTokelauTongaThailandTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands (British)Virgin Islands (USA)Wallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaWestern SamoaYemenYugoslaviaZambiaZimbabwe
Address 1									*
Address 2
City									*
State
*
AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingAmerican SamoaCanal ZoneCommonwealth of the Northern Mariana IslandsFederated States of MicronesiaGuamMarshall IslandsNorthern Mariana IslandsPalauPhilippine IslandsPuerto RicoTrust Territory of the Pacific IslandsVirgin IslandsArmed Forces - AmericasArmed Forces - Europe, Canada, Middle East, AfricaArmed Forces - Pacific
Zip / Postal Code				*
Terms
Acceptance of any contribution, gift or grant is at the discretion of the Minnesota Children's Museum. The Minnesota Children's Museum will not accept any gift unless it can be used or expended consistently with the purpose and mission of the Minnesota Children's Museum.
No irrevocable gift, whether outright or life-income in character, will be accepted if under any reasonable set of circumstances the gift would jeopardize the donor’s financial security.
The Minnesota Children's Museum will refrain from providing advice about the tax or other treatment of gifts and will encourage donors to seek guidance from their own professional advisers to assist them in the process of making their donation.
The Minnesota Children's Museum will accept donations of cash or publicly traded securities. Gifts of in-kind services will be accepted at the discretion of the Minnesota Children's Museum.
Certain other gifts, real property, personal property, in-kind gifts, non-liquid securities, and contributions whose sources are not transparent or whose use is restricted in some manner, must be reviewed prior to acceptance due to the special obligations raised or liabilities they may pose for Minnesota Children's Museum.
The Minnesota Children's Museum will provide acknowledgments to donors meeting tax requirements for property received by the charity as a gift. However, except for gifts of cash and publicly traded securities, no value shall be ascribed to any receipt or other form of substantiation of a gift received by Minnesota Children's Museum.
The Minnesota Children's Museum will respect the intent of the donor relating to gifts for restricted purposes and those relating to the desire to remain anonymous. With respect to anonymous gifts, the Minnesota Children's Museum will restrict information about the donor to only those staff members with a need to know.
The Minnesota Children's Museum will not compensate, whether through commissions, finders' fees, or other means, any third party for directing a gift or a donor to the Minnesota Children's Museum.
Show Terms
Hide Terms
Agree to Terms?
Donation Total:
$1.00
Monthly
Recurring donations will occur for one year. Once the anniversary of the first installment approaches, we will contact you about renewing your gift.
Donate Now
FollowFollowFollow
Pin It on Pinterest
X
